[
    {
        "question": "How many broomsticks are flown in a full game of Quidditch?",
        "options": [
            "Fifteen", 
            "Sixteen", 
            "Fourteen", 
            "Two hundred and Sixty seven" 
        ],
        "imagem": "quidditch",
        "rightAnswer": "Fifteen"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does one say to close the Marauder's Map and make it blank again?",
        "options": [
            "Nox",
            "Nothing to see here",
            "Mischief Managed",
            "Close"
        ],
        "imagem": "map",
        "rightAnswer": "Mischief Managed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Hogwarts house is Terry Boot a member",
        "options": [
            "Slytherin", 
            "Ravenclaw", 
            "Gryffindor", 
            "Hufflepuff" 
        ],
        "imagem": "terry",
        "rightAnswer": "Ravenclaw"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is head of the department of magical games and sports?",
        "options": [
            "Igor Karkaroff",
            "Oliver Wood",
            "Cornelius Fudge",
            "Ludo Bagman"
        ],
        "imagem": "sports",
        "rightAnswer": "Ludo Bagman"
    },
    {
        "question": "A wizard who cannot do magic is known as a: ",
        "options": [
            "Muggle",
            "Wizont",
            "Duddle",
            "Squib"
        ],
        "imagem": "squib",
        "rightAnswer": "Squib"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Bathsheda Babbling?",
        "options": [
            "Muggle Studies Professor",
            "An auror from the Order of the Phoenix",
            "Ancient Runes Professor",
            "An lord of the rings character"
        ],
        "imagem": "bathsheda",
        "rightAnswer": "Ancient Runes Professor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Polyjuice Potion ingredients must be acquired at the full moon?",
        "options": [
            "A bit of whoever you wish to turn into", 
            "Knotgrass", 
            "Fluxweed", 
            "Newt spleen" 
        ],
        "imagem": "potion",
        "rightAnswer": "Fluxweed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which spell summons an object?",
        "options": [
            "Aparecium",
            "Accio",
            "Apparate",
            "Ascendio"
        ],
        "imagem": "accio",
        "rightAnswer": "Accio"
    },
    {
        "question": "Katie Bell is:",
        "options": [
            "A Gryffindor and a half-blood",
            "A Ravenclaw and a pureblood",
            "A Gryffindor and a pureblood",
            "A Hufflepuff and a muggleborn"
        ],
        "imagem": "katie",
        "rightAnswer": "A Gryffindor and a pureblood"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does O.W.L. stand for?",
        "options": [
            "Official Wizarding Level",
            "Ordinary Wizarding Level",
            "Outstanding Wizarding Level",
            "Outstanding Wonderful Luck"
        ],
        "imagem": "owl",
        "rightAnswer": "Ordinary Wizarding Level"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was formerly a headmaster of Hogwarts?",
        "options": [
            "Aberforth Dumbledore",
            "Phineas Nigellus Black",
            "Nicholas de Mimsy-Porpington",
            "Cornelius Fudge"
        ],
        "imagem": "phineas",
        "rightAnswer": "Phineas Nigellus Black"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who played Lord Voldemort in the movies?",
        "options": [
            "Jeremy Irons",
            "Tom Riddle",
            "Gary Oldman",
            "Ralph Fiennes"
        ],
        "imagem": "voldemort",
        "rightAnswer": "Ralph Fiennes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which team from the Ministry of Magic is responsible for modifying the memories of Muggles who have been exposed to magic?",
        "options": [
            "Unspeakables", 
            "Aurors", 
            "Obliviators", 
            "The Wizengamot" 
        ],
        "imagem": "memories",
        "rightAnswer": "Obliviators"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which spell shoots a fireball from the caster's wand?",
        "options": [
            "Lacarnum Inflamarae",
            "Incendio",
            "Incarcerous",
            "Imperio"
        ],
        "imagem": "fire",
        "rightAnswer": "Lacarnum Inflamarae"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Hogwarts house was Moaning Murtle a member of?",
        "options": [
            "Ravenclaw", 
            "Hufflepuff", 
            "Slytherin", 
            "Gryffindor" 
        ],
        "imagem": "moaning",
        "rightAnswer": "Ravenclaw"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year was Ollivanders founded?",
        "options": [
            "382 BC", 
            "465 BC", 
            "57 BC", 
            "712 BC" 
        ],
        "imagem": "ollivanders",
        "rightAnswer": "382 BC"
    },
    {
        "question": "Cuthbert Binns is a professor in what subject?",
        "options": [
            "Muggle Studies",
            "Astronomy",
            "Ancient Runes",
            "History of Magic"
        ],
        "imagem": "binns",
        "rightAnswer": "History of Magic"
    },
    {
        "question": "What number is Harry's vault at the Gringotts Wizarding Bank?",
        "options": [
            "Six hundred and twenty-seven", 
            "Seven hundred and eleven", 
            "Six hundred and eighty-seven", 
            "Seven hundred and thirteen" 
        ],
        "imagem": "gringots",
        "rightAnswer": "Six hundred and eighty-seven"
    }
]
